So we have been making a lot of progress
in building our application.
That we can actually say already that the core functionality
of the app is in fact already working.
So now let's take a breath and think a little bit
about our next step in this short lecture.
So again, the core functionality is what we see here
in this flow chart.
And so that is basically the search functionality,
then also displaying the pagination
and then displaying any recipe that was selected.
And so that we already have working at this point.
And so that is really great progress,
but now let's take it to the next level
and think a little bit about how we will implement
our next features here.
So based on the user stories
that we outlined in the beginning of this project,
our next feature was a functionality
for changing the servings of the displayed recipe.
And that's going to be quite easy.
All we will have to do is to listen
and to handle events on the change servings buttons
and then basically update the recipe and render it again.
Then the next feature is the bookmarking functionality.
And this is going to be yet another one
that will be a little bit complex to implement.
So let's see what we have here.
So starting with the event here more on the left side,
whenever the user bookmarks a certain recipe
then we want to render that bookmarks
in the special bookmarks panel,
and we also want to update the button in the recipe.
And so basically we will then rerender the recipe.
Now then whenever the user clicks one of the bookmarks,
and so that's the other event down there
then we want to render exactly that a recipe
that was clicked, okay?
So here we will need two events
and by the time we reach this functionality
we will, of course seen more detail how it's gonna work.
Then next up, we want to be able to store
this personalized bookmark data in the browser
and also a read it back when the page is loaded
for the next time.
And so that's exactly what is here on this diagram.
So whenever there is a new bookmark,
we basically store all the bookmarks to local storage.
And then when the page loads
then we load all the bookmarks back
from the local storage and render them, all right?
And so that's actually it.
So this is what we will do over the next couple of lectures.
And once we're done with that,
the application will actually almost be finished.
Okay, so that is our plan for the next couple of lectures.
And so let's now go back to code
and implement the functionality
of changing the servings right in the next lecture.